I think GTA is a magical moment for our
culture.
>> So, what's your biggest trade coming up
>> like is going to do phenomenal.
>> What about
>> I'm not excited about I don't own any
right now, but I still think the main
trade is on take two.
>> What are your thoughts on
>> I love to see falling here. I don't know
when I'm going to make my big move to
heavily lever back into it, but it's
probably going to happen at some point
in the next few months.
>> Chris, thank you so much for coming back
on the ice coffee hour.
>> Happy to be here anytime.
>> We forgot to ask you your thoughts on
Tesla.
>> I don't think my like thesis on Tesla
has changed at all. I think only one
thing matters and that's the robot,
right? That's Optimus. And so there's
actually a lot to talk about when it
comes to Optimist and I haven't talked
about it publicly in a bit. Um,
everyone has really strong feelings on
Tesla, so I'm always trying to like I
don't know, be careful with my words
because I think I end up pissing so many
Tesla fanboys off when I say anything
negative.
The truth is, you remember guys, like my
big robotic thesis was mainly around
Optimus and Tesla years ago. Like I was
super
long Tesla on the hope that Optimus
could essentially equate to a $10
trillion valuation just at Tesla, just
the Optimus division, right? If they
were to execute on that. The the truth
is um at least from my evaluation of the
program and my intel and everything that
I've been hearing for the past two plus
years the Optimus program has been in
shambles. The Optimus program has not
performed. Uh they've lost a lot of
their top talent. From what I understand
there has been a lot of internal
frustration. uh between the team and
between between the team and Elon as it
relates to progress, as it relates to
strategy on the robot, as it relates to
to the hands specifically and hand
strategy. Contrary to what you might
have heard recently from a big
influencer who claims to have seen a
video and tells you that Optimus is a
year and a half further along than any
other robot, I don't think that person
necessarily knows what he's talking
about because my intel tells me the
exact opposite. Uh we were supposed to
get an Optimus update publicly in March
and April this year. It didn't come. It
seems like we're nowhere close to seeing
this next gen of Optimus and that they
are far behind and that there are still
way more questions and answers as it
relates to getting Optimus to that point
of a truly scalable hardware platform,
right? It's it's it's not it's not ready
for scale yet. We're ready to show
>> the Tesla play is really just a humanoid
robot play.
>> That's it for me. That's it. I
>> how much more room would the company
have to grow if it were if it were
strictly off of the cars?
>> Yeah, cuz aren't they doing crazy stuff
with full self-driving and subscription
revenue and they got the robo taxis?
>> Yeah. I mean, I think that's they're
doing fine there, but I don't think
you're going to see a meaningful lift in
valuation coming from that. I think a
lot of that is baked into the current
day's valuation at Tesla. So if you were
to remove Optimus, you can say what is
self-driving reasonably worth right now
when you have to assess the competition.
When we were talking about, you know,
full self-driving, robo taxi, and how
big that industry sector is years ago,
we always kind of thought that Tesla
would be so far advanced,
>> so further along than anyone else. Do
you agree that that's not the case
today? I mean, we can say that Tesla
maybe is in the pole position from a
cost standpoint uh in terms of robo taxi
if their plans play out. But guys, look
at the competition. It's meaningful
globally. Whether you look at the
competition here in terms of Whimo and
others entering the space or if you look
at the competition in China, it's
massive, right? And China is no longer
just about China. the rest of the world
has shown that they're open to kind of
taking these Chinese cars or taking
these Chinese products. So there's real
meaningful competition on driverless now
that we didn't think would be going neck
to neck with Tesla 5 years ago when we
were having these conversations. So like
I just don't know how we would value
that when the moat is no longer as big
as it once was.
I think
generalized robotics, humanoids
specifically, I think the TAM is so
massively large that if Tesla were to
fully execute on the Optimus vision,
they have every opportunity to be in a
pole position and to be a top one or two
company in the space, but they just
haven't executed yet. We have to be
honest.
>> What do you think about Apple right now?
>> Yeah, they just got the new CEO.
>> Yes. $56 million pay package, by the
way.
>> That's fine. I mean, that's nothing in
the big scheme of Apple, right? So,
that's cool.
>> So, you're saying he's underpaid?
>> Yeah. I think it's I don't I just think
it's I just think it's nonmaterial. I
think it's nonmaterial. What do I think
about Apple? Nothing right now. I think
Apple has a great business. They're a
cash cow. They've been fully optimized
to be the cash cow that they are. they
haven't taken a lot of huge risk which
we might look back and think was a good
thing.
>> I I I don't know. I just don't have
strong feelings. I mean what's happening
at Apple right this second that we think
can propel the company meaningfully as a
growth company the next 5 years. I'm not
sure we have the answer to that
question. So like I'm not excited about
Apple. I don't own any Apple right now.
I think it's a fine company. It's just
not a company that has something that
has potential to be wildly great that
the market is underestimating in my
opinion right now today.
>> I just have a hard time believing that
they're not working on something
different, unique, with high growth
potential behind the scenes.
>> Okay. So, I was really upset cuz I
thought for a couple years that there is
no way that Apple wasn't cooking up a
robot division that was meaningful
behind the scenes because there's no
company on earth that has the trust of
consumers that has the ecosystem to pull
off a home robot like Apple does. Even
if it's 10 years away, I don't care 5
years away, 8 years away.
>> If you're going to bring a robot into
your home, that robot is going to be
able to listen. is going to be able to
see a lot of really personal stuff. This
is something that no one really talks
about. Also, there's a high level of
safety, right, that you're going to want
in the home with your pets, with your
kids, with elderly, even with yourself.
Um, Apple has something that I think no
other company on earth could could get
quickly. And so, they have a massive
advantage there. They also are
phenomenal hardware company, right? Like
I am just so confused when when I found
out this is and this is like a year ago,
a little over a year ago when I found
out that as like for sure that they
still basically had an arm in a box was
their robot program. I was like you got
to be kidding me. I thought for sure
they had something deep secret that they
had moved the entire automotive team.
remember they had that huge team in
automotive and I know that they moved a
lot of that team to robotics.
>> I was like for sure they have to be
cooking up something more interesting
than that and it just doesn't feel like
they are unless something has changed
recently. But that would get me hyped on
Apple because when we look at
generalized robotics
uh and humanoids, they're two very you
have the the commercialized sector which
is a multi-dea trillion dollar sector
and then you have the home sector which
is equally as big. But Apple is in this
unique position to distribute robots
into the home at scale in a trustworthy
way. Cuz think about if you're going to
put a robot in your house, what company
would you trust more than Apple with
their history, their closed ecosystem,
right? Like also to already connect to
all the personal data that they already
have on you cuz there's only a few
companies that have that level of data,
right? I I'm just so stunned at the lack
of vision there. I I don't know what
happened that they're just missing out
on embodied AI. They missed out on AI,
but they didn't have to miss out on
embodied AI, which is potentially going
to be larger than AI because embodied AI
is going to have massive moes involved.
What about Amazon? I found this really
interesting because you've been calling
this for a really, really, really long
time now. And recently, they had
earnings. They destroyed earnings and
they kind of like on top of that I would
say quelled a lot of the fears around
the company of Amazon like with the
capex spending and stuff like that. So
they they crushed the report and so the
stock popped. It didn't even pop as much
as I thought.
>> No, now it's been down
>> and since then it is just steadily
declined and now it's nearly back where
it was before the pop. It's certainly
back where it was a few weeks before it
popped with earnings. And it's like it
like it priced it but then it just
immediately went back down. I'm curious
to hear your thoughts on that. What do
you think's going on with the investor
sentiment?
>> It's wild, right?
>> Are you still invested?
>> Okay, hold on before Chris answers that
quick PSA. You know how we always ask
the guests what they're invested in? You
can see exactly what Graham and I are
invested in right now. Exactly. There's
this app called Blossom Social and
they're partnering with us on this and
it's basically like a social media for
investors where you could see exactly
what people own, not just what they say
they own.
>> Grim and I both uploaded our entire
portfolio so you can see everything that
we're invested in and whether it's up or
down dayto-day, which means we will
finally be able to see which one of us
is the better investor.
>> Come on, we already know who that is.
Jack,
>> you know what, Graeme, you are right. We
do know which one of us is better.
Anyway, over a million people have
downloaded it and it was actually ranked
one of Canada's fastest growing
startups. And what's really cool about
this is that it was started by a
subscriber who reached out. We started
talking. He told me that he was watching
for almost 10 years at this point, got
inspired, started the idea, and now look
at it. So, I just think it's neat to be
able to support the people who also
supported us when we were just starting.
And now seeing all the success of this,
wanted to be a part of it. I uploaded my
portfolio. I love it. Plus, there is
another reason that we're telling you
this. Caleb Hammer is on Blossom. And
right now, he has more followers than
us, and we cannot let that happen. So,
this is the mission. We need to pass
Caleb Hammer. That's the goal. That's
all we need. The app is totally free. It
cost you nothing. And you can see how
Jack and I are doing on there. We got to
catch up to Caleb Hammer, please. The
link is down below in the description.
And it cost you nothing. It's free.
Thank you so much. And now, let's get
back to the conversation.
>> Are you still invested? Oh yeah. I I
mean I'm I'm out of my hyper levered
options position like your weekly call
options.
>> Yeah. That that that's you know that
that's all fully exited. I have a much
smaller levered position in Amazon now.
Uh it's still levered. I think Amazon is
the perfect representation of the modern
investor. The modern investor
requires such a heavy level of dopamine
hit with their investments that Amazon
just is never sexy enough for them. Like
it's wild to me. Amazon's just not
willing to deliver what the modern
investor wants. The modern investor is
thinking in their head shortterm they
want 3x. They want 4x potential. They
want even with options they want 7 8 10x
potential.
Amazon is not one of those companies
because of its size. You have a company
like Tesla. You have a company like
SpaceX that's of almost equivalent size,
but Elon puts out a narrative, whether
you believe it or not, that makes you
think it could be a $30 trillion
company, right? I don't think it can be,
but
investors are buying it to some extent.
the investors are willing to get excited
about SpaceX because they buy this this
kind of blue sky vision about infinite
like
value right in the universe that only
SpaceX can deliver. So, Amazon's not
doing that, right? Amazon, they're the
there are these companies that the
market just completely forgets about
because they just don't have that level
of sexiness and they're just not
punching the dopamine meter for the
average investor. I personally love it
because I know that there will be
moments when the market's like, "Oh,
shoot. Amazon really is special. Oh,
wow. Those are big numbers. This is
real." and it gives me opportunities to
lever back into Amazon over and over
again. So, I love to see Amazon falling
here. I don't know when I'm going to
make my big move to heavily lever back
into it, but it's probably going to
happen at some point in the next few
months.
>> Is there a certain price that you would
relever back into Amazon?
>> For me, it's not so much about price.
I'm looking at what's taking the stock
down. So, the stock first got taken down
because of a story that came out out of
the North Carolina DA's office or
whatever, right? They're suing Amazon
because they claim that Amazon was
screwing advertisers out of like a penny
per transaction
>> by telling them that there was a nominal
difference between the winning bid and
the next bid, but then actually
proactively making that spread larger
over time, which is like deceptive
advertising. And there's potentially $20
billion in money that was taken from
advertisers. So that's not a good story,
but that's not a story that I find to be
particularly impactful for the long term
of Amazon, right? So like that case is
going to go on for years. It will
probably get settled and in 6 months, no
one's going to be thinking about it or
talking about it anymore. Yet the stock
got hit pretty heavy on that one news
story. Now today, the market comes out
with the 10-year rate
>> higher than anticipated. And again,
people are thinking Amazon is going to
be one of the companies that's hurt by
that. So, I'm like, well, I just keep
adding a little bit of Amazon every time
this happens because if Amazon gets hit
on a story that I don't think is
particularly meaningful, then I'm going
to go further into Amazon. If it gets
hit by something that I think is
meaningful, I'll reassess and maybe
lighten up on my Amazon. Right? The
reason why I don't think interest rates
matter, I think we talked about this on
the last episode, for a company like
Amazon is Amazon is increasing their
level. If you believe them, and I do,
I've said this for a long time. Yes, the
borrowing cost is is is getting larger
for a company like Amazon. Also of
course the opportunity cost of being
invested in a risk asset like Amazon uh
becomes higher when
you can get a higher rate on on no risk
money obviously which is what's
happening
>> but compared to the increase in growth
at a company like Amazon due to this a
AI super cycle these small halfpoint
moves are ultimately meaningless okay so
I think historically when You look at a
company like Amazon and you see a half
point interest rate move. That's bad.
But we are not in historical times. Like
we are in a very special moment when
Amazon is increasing their growth from
like 11% a year and a half ago to like
16% or something like that next year. So
like a half point move isn't the thing
we should be paying attention to. But I
know why the market does because for 20
years that mattered. So you have this
like muscle memory of higher interest
rates. Bad for Amazon and other
companies like it. But Amazon should be
a class of company that is accelerating
their growth at such a high rate where
we should not be as concerned about
interest rate movements as we were in
the past.
>> So what's your biggest trade coming up?
I noticed you were posting about GTA.
>> I Yeah. So, got get a lot of heat on
this. I always get so much heat these
days. Like, I don't know what's going
on.
>> You got more people following your every
move. They see what you're doing and
they're like, I'm going to bet my life
savings on that.
>> I think I need to like recalibrate what
you just said because I'm not used to
it.
>> And it's something that I just got to
get used to and not take personally.
I'll say this,
the market is dumber than it's ever been
because everybody has a strong opinion,
but so few people, less than ever, are
actually willing to do the real work.
And I'm not saying that I'm right about
GTA and Take 2, but what I'm saying is
at least I did the work and I could
point you to to
the rationale behind my thesis. And
every time someone questions me on my
take two GTA
thesis, I'm like, "Well, what's yours?"
Like, like, you're saying it's baked
into the stock price. You keep saying
the words. It's already baked into the
price. What's baked into the price?
30 million launch quarter units moved,
40 million, 50 million. What average
revenue per user year 1 is baked into
the like no one can answer me like
what's the benchmark?
>> I feel like the answer is just a lot
because everyone's been hyping this
word. That's not a word.
>> It is though. It's just it's this it's
this infinite amount of hype that people
are just attributing to this stock
because GTA has just been teasing this
for years. And it's it's not an amount
you could measure just because it's
infinite.
>> There is no number. I I want to sell my
my company to you and there's an
infinite you can't even measure
>> the amount of hype. Trust me though,
it's infinite.
We could see it's infinite because
people are talking about it for years.
>> This is so great.
>> It's become a meme of like, oh, this
happened before GTA did and for years.
So, you don't think that's already been
priced in to the nth degree for years?
>> There has to be a number. Okay, you're
part of it.
>> It's just But there's so much excitement
that you can't pinpoint it to be like
this is how much the excitement's worth.
It's infinite.
>> I love that you just said this because
you are actually the most pragmatic,
most rational, smartest guy, and even
you are part of this problem that I'm
talking about.
>> It's not a problem, but it's a reality.
>> It's the reality that you cannot price
that stock accurately at all because
there's so much hype going into it.
>> Okay. So, okay. So, let me let me let me
give you the inverse of what you just
said. If what you said is factually
true, then you essentially a guaranteed
lock to short the company because it's
baked in infinite. So no matter what the
number is that they actually hit, it's
going to be a disappointment.
>> I almost tend to agree,
but I would never short because you
never know. It could be short-term hype
that just skyrockets this thing and it
becomes a meme a little bit. like GoPro
was becoming this like, oh, let's yolo
into GoPro cuz Markiplier is doing it.
It's like you never know. You can't
predict that. But but
>> okay, here's what I will admit to.
Whether I agree with you or not, what
you just said is the new norm and it's
the reality of today's market and I need
to accept that. And that's what I've
come to learn over the last few days.
Now guys, I'm going to age myself, but I
was trading GTA's release on Take 2 in
1999. Okay? You don't know this about
me, but like trading video game launches
used to be one of my biggest trades back
in the late '9s, early 2000s, right?
I've been doing this a really long time.
And back then, the people that traded
Take 2 Interactive on GTA were really
smart. And we had a very like uh a
structural benchmark for what was
anticipated and who thought they would
come out above or below. And we were all
placing our bets and we all put a
tremendous amount of work into whether
or not we think the company would beat
or miss based on this many units moved.
that no longer exists because now every
investor, yeah, we do have unit
estimates that range between 30 million
and 50 million for calendar year 1 for
GTA, right? I personally think uh that
based on the initial reactions of the
first gameplay that came out last week
that we will be at the high end of that,
if not beyond the high end of that,
which is why I took a long position in
in in take two. But the market isn't
even thinking about that because the
market today's market in the people
investing in take 2 don't even know what
the projected unit sales are by sellside
banks or by analyst or like they don't
even care. They're just like they're
they're investing in take 2 or shorting
it or talking about it based on vibes.
And it drives me actually insane because
I read through, no joke, like 30,000
organic comments on that Netflix
trailer. And I'm so optimistic based on
what I read that I was like, this is a
best case scenario. And my entire thesis
on Take 2 in GTA
revolves around depth of interest in
gameplay, which by the way is yet to be
determined, but I only have 27 minutes
so far to determine that. And based on
the reactions on that 27 minutes, I
think it's highly likely that we are
going to have a really strong depth of
interest in gameplay, the the deeper
that interest, the easier it will be for
Take 2 and Rockstar to monetize that
game when they come out with online. And
the big question is, can they monetize
it at $20 per active monthly user or $60
per active monthly user? And if it's
closer to $60 per monthly active user,
if the number of active users is like 50
60 million plus, dude, you could see
Take 2 stock double. So like I'm being
very rational and pragmatic about the
trade about like my scenario analysis
and like what cues I'm looking for to
identify that scenario playing out
versus that scenario out. The problem is
that almost no other investor is doing
what I'm doing. So even if I'm right
right now, it's not going to be
reflective in the stock because I crunch
the numbers a day before everybody else
cuz I'm like I'm going through doing
what I do and I'm thinking, okay, I just
fast traded this. I I think this
scenario is going to play out and 3 days
later everyone else is going to see it.
Well, 3 days later, no one's seeing it
cuz no one everyone's too lazy to do the
work that I'm doing. They're not even
running scenario analysis. They're not
even doing any type of real work to
assess if they're likely to come up
above the the recognized benchmark for
unit sales for for for arpoo. Like no
one does the work anymore.
>> Yeah. But but that means all of your
work is for nothing because people are
buying based off vibes.
>> Yes.
>> And that's already priced in and you
can't price in the vibes.
>> Yeah. And so like I have to be honest
with the reality of the market and
that's something that I've come to terms
with over the fa past few days because
what happened guys was there was a rumor
that came out that they're going to
delay online for 2 years and it's not
because they can't put out online if if
if that rumor were to be true it's
because Rockstar wants it to be true.
It's because they they think there's a
strategic reason to hold two years. I
don't think they're holding out two
years. I don't think that's going to
happen with GTA 5. They released online
I think like 17 days after the console
the normal version came out. Okay. So,
and by the way, what's really
fascinating here is like like Rockstar
and GTA, they were the innovators that
took microtransactions
to AAAS console gaming and prove that
you could generate billions of dollars
from a AAA console game through GTA.
Even this year, 13 years after GTA 5
came out, they're generating like 600
million from microtransactions from a
13-year-old game. Okay. So, if you run
the numbers, I think like when I run all
my scenario analysis out, I think
there's a reasonable shot that they
could land somewhere between two and $3
billion a year through microtransactions
with GTA 6. Okay. with the online
version. That's on top of selling 50 60
million potential copies at an average
price of like 90s something dollars
because almost everyone's buying the
$100 copy versus the $80 copy, right?
And so there was also news that came out
from Sensor Tower. Sensor Tower is like
the tracking service for games. And
again, no one does their research, so no
one even knows where these numbers come
from. Sensor Tower is a company that
historically only does research on Steam
games. Okay? So, when they do when they
put out their estimates on how many
pre-sales of a Steam game, they're
usually off by 3 or 4%. This is the
first time ever that they're putting out
an estimate in the last few months. They
just started doing this on a console
game. So, the methodology they're using
is unknown. They don't have access to
all the things you have access to on a
Steam game, which is they've been doing
it for years and years and years. They
they've been able to refine their
numbers, right? We don't even know if
they're right or not. But what they're
saying is that the pre-sales are only
like 4.8 million. And people are like,
"Dude, that feels low." Well, of course
it's low. Even if they're right,
it doesn't matter because this is only a
digital game. Who the hell was
pre-ordering a digital game? You go back
to GTA 5 in 2013 and I want to say they
had 7 million pre-sales, but that was a
hard game. That wasn't a digital game.
You're going to you're going to
pre-order that game because if you don't
pre-order it, you might not have it on
day one. This is only digital. You don't
need to pre-order.
>> So, why don't you invest just a little
downstream of that and think, well,
people are probably going to be drinking
a lot of energy drinks. People are
probably going to be buying comfier
chairs, better monitors, and like go a
step beyond
this.
>> You can and there are some actually
really
there are some interesting secondary
trades here
>> or things to short like if people are
spending more money on video games, you
know, probably short
>> short Barnes & Noble.
>> Yeah. Or like the dating market somehow.
Maybe like, you know, the the apps are
really going to see, you know, lower
numbers.
>> Oh, that that's fair. So, so
>> I was thinking about we're actually
going to do a separate like whole dumb
money just another GTA episode. We're
talking about all these secondary
trades, but like I'll just give you some
of them like like Door Dash
>> is going to do phenomenal. I actually
told my restaurant group, and I bet they
haven't done it yet because they never
listened to me, but I told them that I
wanted to have a GTA delivery special
where we come up with like packages of
food that dudes would want to eat while
playing GTA.
No,
>> something that doesn't get your fingers
sticking.
>> Yeah. But listen, it's it's just a way
to have fun with it. We can do social
media, right? And like I want every
gamer in Dallas
>> pizzas.
>> Yeah, dude. Dude, we already have we
already have all the pizzas. We have all
that stuff at my restaurant. So like I
want every GTA gamer in Dallas thinking
Chelsea Corner, Milo's, let's order from
them cuz I saw their Instagram. I saw
that they're doing GTA specials. Let's
just make it fun, man. Let's just lean
into this because like for 60 days,
dude, do you know how much Door Dash is
going to be ordered in America? Okay,
it's like all right, let's just say they
do. Let's just say they do 40. Let's
just say they do 30 million by but on
the first week. Okay. Roughly onethird
of historically of GTA's gamers are in
the US. Twothirds are are foreign.
Again, I honestly feel that I'm the only
person that knows all this. Like cuz
investors are so lazy. Do they even read
the earnings report? Do they even know
anything about Take 2 Interactive? I'm
just like so many investors will get on
X and start chiming off at me. I'm like,
have you even done one minute of actual
work on what you're talking about? I
know so much about this franchise. I
have 26 years 27 years of work that I've
done on GTA. Okay, I might be totally
wrong, but I'm informed. You know what
I'm saying? Like, and people that are
mouththing off at me, maybe they're
right. Maybe they'll get lucky and
they're right, but like they're not they
haven't even done the work. I'm like,
can we at least have an intelligent
conversation? I would love nothing more,
nothing more, and I've asked people to
do this than to actually comment on my
exost on GTA with wellthoughtout
devil's advocate takes using data and
perspective and like benchmarks.
I invite that. You guys know that. I
love that. That's what I love. But I
can't have intelligent discourse with
investors anymore because it feels like
there's no intelligent investors.
Everybody's surface level. Everyone's
for vibes. Everyone's for dopamine hits.
And like it sucks. I love that there's
so many investors, but I wish people
would just chill out and actually do a
little bit of homework and let's have
some intelligent discourse on like these
narratives and these thesis and these
takes and like these trades that like
I'm putting on or they're putting on.
But I think Door Dash can connect. 10
million guys in the US are going to be
playing GTA non-stop for like starting
November whatever 17th or the end of the
year.
>> Is that a confirmed release date or
could this be something they're going to
be going to be January?
>> It's Listen, it's always possible.
>> But dude, if they delay that, that would
be catastrophic because you want to
release it going into the holiday season
for so many reasons. Kids are getting
off of school. It's winter time. Like
you're stuck at your house. Like half
the country. It's miserable. You want to
you want a game, right? Like
>> dude, they need they can't miss that. If
they miss that release, Take Two is
going to fall through the floor. No
doubt about it. 10 million guys ordering
food nonstop. Okay. It's definitely
going to help Door Dash. Probably going
to help Uber through Uber Eats, right?
Um there are some other plays here too.
You saw that that this movie studios
were preparing saying that they were
expecting
>> yes it was going to impact viewership
>> there there's probably some pretty fun
secondary trades to be had but I still
think the main trade is on take two. I
just don't have any sense for timing
because it's really difficult for me to
assess when other investors are going to
see even if I'm right when will other
investors start to see what I'm seeing
will take 2 has been pretty quiet with
numbers so will they even come out and
say we have this many they haven't done
it have this many pre-orders they said
one thing they said something like the
number of pre-orders I think this was in
the first week was unprecedented.
Unprecedented. Okay. So, like, and
again, who the hell is pre-ordering a
digital game? You could just order it
the day of. There's no difference. So,
like, I think the fact that they have
almost 5 million pre-orders according to
Sensor Tower, and maybe it's six or
seven or eight cuz they've never done
this before with a console game and and
had a history.
Like, I think that's pretty great. Um,
and I think there could be a moment here
when the market wakes up to take two.
I'll tell you the thing I'm most excited
about about GTA though. You could tell
me if you think I'm wrong. I've been
talking about this in a lot of different
ways. There is this going back to the SW
remember I brought that swatch watch
back to you guys and we're talking about
how people just love to wait hours for
Fro yo or for like the new hot
sweatshirt release or the or the skin
care release.
>> Trader Joe's bag,
>> dude. Trader Joe, it doesn't matter what
it people love. Why? Why are they doing
this? Like I think people are really
thirsting for like human connection and
a cultural moment of connectivity where
we're all doing something together cuz
we rarely do things together anymore. We
used to all watch TV on Thursday night
with Seinfeld and Friends and all that
stuff and like nobody and then even Game
of Thrones, right? Or whatever it was.
Like we have so few cultural moments
where we're able to bond as humans. I
think the Olympics was one of those for
a little bit this year and it was really
cool to see or like when you have these
limited releases people love lining up I
think because they just want to feel
like next to other humans that care
about the same thing they do. I think
GTA is a magical moment for our culture
and that is the most crossgeneral
crossgenerational game we've ever seen.
There are guys in their like 40, they
grew up with this, right? Like the the
first GTA, multiple generations grew up
with GTA. I'm reading comments where
guys are like, "Dude, I had to get
permission from my parents to play this
game." And they're like, "No, I'm not
getting permission from my girlfriend
now." You know what I'm saying? Like,
it's really funny. But I think what's
going to happen is people are go this
game's going to come out and if you're
not playing it, you're going to feel
that you're getting left out of
something really special, like a
historic moment, at least a guy moment,
right?
>> Are you going to play it?
>> So, I don't play a lot of video games
myself. But I will tell you this. I will
tell you this. Hold on. I did play I
have played GTA historically.
>> And for research or for fun?
>> For fun. No, for fun. Which one? Um,
>> going all the way back to 99. Okay. And
then I play GTA 5, but now I have a son.
He's 16 and all of his buddies are going
to be playing.
>> I will be in the room.
>> Okay. Like, so whether I I will play it
a little bit myself,
>> but whether I'm like actively playing it
myself, trust me, I'm going to be in the
room with my son and his friends, like
living through them, cuz like I will
almost have more fun watching them play
than like I will get on and play some,
but I'm not going to be like spending
hours upon hours like melting into the
GTA world.
>> That did remind me. I remember in high
school there was something. I think it
was called Halo Tuesday and it was all
the kids took off the Tuesday to play
Halo and it wasn't just like my school.
It was like the whole county Halo
Tuesday to play Halo. Dude, I we don't
get this much anymore, guys. Like I just
think this is going to be one of those
cultural moments that people lean into.
And what's going to happen is a lot of
guys don't have friends to hang out
with. We live in a lonely system. We
know this. Everyone's going through what
they call it the male
>> loneliness epidemic.
>> And so if you're one of the many many
millions, probably tens of millions of
guys that are sitting alone in your
apartment or your house and you you're
part of that epidemic, you feel a sense
of connectivity by buying GTA and
playing it. I hate to say it, but like
you're doing the same thing that every
other guy is doing from November,
whatever through the end of the year,
and you're part of something and you're
not alone. And you can go on forums and
talk about it. You could like when the
online comes out, you could be part of
that. I actually think this is even
though this game is kind of evil in many
ways, I think it's an important positive
thing for connectivity for this this
younger generation and the older
generation as well. And it's something
we can all connect to together and
hopefully I can make money off of.
>> I agree. I think if you're not a part of
these cultural movements, then you do
kind of get FOMO. Like even as crazy as
this comparison is, but similar to
Adrian's kickback. Do you remember that?
>> No.
>> Oh, I remember that. Adrian's kickback.
It was a thing that was posted on like
Tik Tok and everyone. It was a It was
something I think that meant to be a
text from one individual to another.
>> I thought it was Facebook or maybe it
was Facebook, but it accidentally got
posted publicly. It might have been a
Facebook post that was supposed to be a
message or private Facebook and it was
like, "Hey bro, are you going to go to
Adrian's kickback?"
>> And then it just went like wildfire all
over social media. And like then
actually I think like tens of thousands
if not hundreds of thousands of people
all met in Huntington Beach for Adrian's
Kickback. I
>> do remember this. This like seven years
ago maybe.
>> Yeah, maybe a little less than that. It
might have been like 2021ish.
Uh but yeah, everyone met up for
Adrian's kickback and then ever they,
you know, not rioted, but like it ended
up not in the greatest way, but it was
one of those things that like you felt
like you were a part of something if you
went or if you knew about it, if you
knew someone that went. You didn't want
to know that Adrian's kickback was going
on that night and not check Snap Maps or
check like, you know, Tik Tok to see
what it was like. I feel like also
gaming is about to shift and this is
probably a final moment for this style
of game too. Like no one's going to
spend 13 years building a game ever
again. Uh Rockstar won't do it. This is
the last GTA that will ever come out.
They'll do nothing but expansion packs.
No, they could they'll they'll expand
off this.
>> They won't spend 13 years. But couldn't
AI eventually get so good that it's
changing in the moment and you could
create a video game just like that that
evolves? I think that I think that's
what this I think that's what they'll do
here. They'll use AI to evolve this
beyond, right? But they're not gonna be
I don't think it's going to be like GTA
7.
>> I think they've come out and basically
said that's the plan is not to have GTA
7, but to like build this out. They'll
spend a decade using AI to do all that
stuff and they'll expand to other
cities, but it'll be part of this
universe um and this character set
>> I think. Um, but it is kind of like a
last moment and I think it's almost
spiritual. I know that sounds crazy, but
like in a world in a time when we don't
have a lot of like spiritual moments
like especially for guys, I think guys
need this right now. And I cuz listen,
you're talking to someone that's read
more comments, like actual comments, not
from investors, but from people that are
just regular people who watched that
video on Netflix or YouTube and just
shared their comments like about how
excited they are about how they've been
waiting for this. And like I think a lot
of these people that like shoot for
clicks by saying outrageous things like
once you get past that the the breath
and depth of interest in this release
there's something really special about
to happen guys. People been waiting 10
plus years for this. Like they have and
it's going to be a magical moment. And I
think people are underappreciating
how big this can be for Take 2
Interactive because they could generate
billions a year off microtransactions
if the game play is as good as it
appears to be. And again, all the things
that people are saying is a negative, I
have have a rebuttal against. Like
people are like, "Oh, but the story line
doesn't look." They didn't give you any
story line. It was a 27minute
like gameplay. There's specifically not
giving you any story line, guys. Um like
you could look through every single
thing that someone said might be a
negative about this and it just makes no
sense to me at all. Um I thought it was
probably a 10 of 10 trailer in terms of
what I was expecting. I was expecting
something way worse. And I was expecting
the backlash of that 27minute trailer to
be pretty rough. And I was stunned how
all the truly
like like engaged gamers, the people
that do this for a living, the people
that love it, like their actual organic
reactions to this were phenomenal.
>> How much money do you expect to put on
that investment? I mean, I have millions
in it right now, but it's just an equity
trade. I could see myself I'm This is
not going to be an Amazon type of thing,
guys, right? But like, I could see
myself putting a million dollar options
trade on Take Two. In my head, I have
this little thing. I kind of want to
make a million dollars or more on on on
GTA. Like, I was just It's a stupid
thing, but I was like, I don't play the
game, but I play the stock. So, like I I
want to make a million dollars on G on
the GTA release. if there's an
opportunity to do it. Um, I'll let you
know if I pull that off or maybe I might
lose a million.
>> Would you be upset if you only made
$875,000?
>> No, I wouldn't be upset. But like I kind
of like just
>> But you want that million,
>> you know? Like you you know guys that
like part of this is a game for me. I
love it and I have fun with it. So like
in my head I'm like it would be cool to
make a million dollars on GTA. Yeah,
it'd be cool. And like so like in my
head I'm trying to make a million
dollars on GTA. Um, that's how I'm
playing the game.
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> It's actually really perfect timing
because we filmed with Steve Hamilton
recently and he said the one license
plate he couldn't get was GTA IRL and
right after the podcast I looked online
in Vegas. It was available. No.
>> And so I bought the license plate GTA
space IRL.
>> What car are you putting it on?
>> Probably the Lotus Avora.
>> The Miami blue Lotus Avora with orange
accents. It's kind of a crazy car to put
GTA IRL,
>> but it makes me think, man, the timing.
If I get that plate at the same time as
the release, part of me is thinking
maybe I should just flip that plate
>> and just post it online and say like,
who wants this plate? See what I can get
for
>> So, not flip it to someone that's going
to use it in Nevada, but someone that
would buy it as like
>> No, no, it has to be used in Nevada.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Because it's state specific, so it says
Nevada on it. If someone is registering
a car in Nevada and they want GTA IRL,
how much is that plate worth? Steve
couldn't get it in Chicago. If I get it
in Nevada, I'm I'm assuming it's going
to be approved because they didn't say
no.
>> Dude, that is so badass. Like you got
that. That's
>> I think the plate's got to be worth like
five grand.
>> Dude, it Could you imagine having that
in Florida?
Oh, dude, that
>> Florida LA would be another one.
>> That'd be insane. I'm going I Have you
checked Texas? I got to do that like the
second we're done taping. Dude, that
would be cool. I don't know if it's
appropriate for my pickup truck, but I
will.
>> How about you should get it, but only
put it on your car if you make a million
>> in GTA. And if you don't, you could
always just sell. I guarantee there is
so many people here with exotics.
>> Can you sell a license plate though?
>> GTA IRL is not available in Florida.
>> How about Texas? Whoever is watching
this, if you're not in Nevada or Texas
or Chicago, look it up because I I
actually think it's a pretty funny
plate.
>> It's an awesome plate.
>> Uh Steve said it
>> it's not available.
>> And then show the
>> That's cool.
>> Do a Yeah,
>> that would be cool.
>> That's an awesome plate.
>> That that that's what it should look
like.
>> Oh, that's so clean.
>> Especially in the black. What I really
wanted in Vegas is they have a police
badge license plate. It's black with a
police badge on the lefth hand side. I
wanted GTA IRL with the police badge,
but you could only have like four
characters on that.
>> Oh,
>> so it was a little short, but I wanted
that one. I thought it would be perfect.
>> That's clean, dude. That's It's pretty
sweet.
>> What are your thoughts on GoPro?
>> No thoughts. I mean, I
>> just vibes.
>> 100% just vibes. People were texting me
the GoPro chart and I was like, "Oh god,
here we go again." And so, like, every
time this happens, I get so annoyed if
it actually ends up running that I have
to go buy some just for my FOMO cuz I
know what's going to happen. My entire
feed's going to get flooded. Like, what
if GoPro went to $4, $5?
>> It It would annoy me so much. So, I have
to buy just enough to where it won't
annoy me, but not too much to where I
care if it doesn't happen. And that's
exactly what I did.
>> How much did you buy?
>> I bought uh I think it was like $40,000
of GoPro and I sold it. And I think I
made the tiniest amount of money on it.
Like I got to look to see if it was a
profit or loss. I think it was a slight
profit. You know what's really
interesting to me is that Markiplier
bought 8.5% of the company, but when he
bought in the market cap of GoPro was
only like 60 million bucks. So, he
invested probably around $8 million in
GoPro. I don't know his affiliation with
GoPro or if he just liked the company or
if he talked to someone. And uh because
at eight and a half% that's very
intentional that he's going public about
his
>> investment. Yeah. To that degree. So, I
think that was definitely a publicity
play. It's not like I just really like
the stock that much, maybe, but it
didn't cost him that much money. I mean,
we're talking about like he put like $5
million in GoPro.
>> Yeah. And he won, right?
>> He did. And he turned that into probably
$20 million total.
>> It's It's a insane trade. Honestly, it's
a it's a risky trade,
>> but I feel like I'm just I'm just saying
if you came out and said, "Hey, I put $5
million in this stock and it made you
like a 10% owner in this company."
>> I'm not saying you should do that. It's
just not my thing.
>> But if it comes out like Chris Camilo
buys 10% in that,
>> are you advocating for it? I'm just I'm
not saying you should do but I'm just
hypothetically
>> it comes out that you own like a big
majority you know you're a majority that
dude that's a you know what
>> I don't
>> if if you think it's a great idea
>> the only time I considered something
like that and it was during the pandemic
was Build-a- Bear. I actually I I went
Holy crap.
>> I went really deep into Build-A-Bear.
Like I was interviewing Build-A-Bear
stores constantly.
>> You would be probably a billionaire.
>> I know. So like the one of the top
Build-A-Bear investors was a friend and
we were sharing intel all the time and I
was like, "Dude, this company is
insanely underval." I had a huge trade
on Build-A-Bear. Like I made a insane
amount of money on Build-A-Bear during
the pandemic, but I was like, they're
just like one hit product away. Like
they it doesn't take much to move the
needle for that company. It was crazy
how low it was valued. And I was and I
had some guys, some hedge fun guys,
they're like, "Dude, you should just buy
a piece of like I had a plan for
Build-A-Bear, like like what we can do
with them." And they're like, "Dude, you
should do it." Like and I was like, "It
would work, but I'm I don't want I don't
want the weight of that on my
shoulders." like I don't want a job
again. I don't want to be a CEO of a
company again. Like I'm those days are
long gone. But that would have been that
would have been fun cuz I was going to
like I was going to merge Build-A-Bear
into the collectible space and we're
going to do all kinds of crazy collabs
cuz I didn't feel like they were doing
enough collabs and I was like there are
some wild Build a Bear collabs that we
could be doing that would be so easy to
do. we would get so much traction on
them. And I was gonna basically take the
Crocs model and move it to Build-A-Bear.
And
I think it would have worked. And they
do a little bit of that, but they don't
do enough of it. I I feel like I feel
like they just need a really good
marketing content social arm to that
company that they just they've just
never really had. they go for these big
brand deals with like Disney or whatever
when they should be doing like really
like creative, gutsy, cool
collaborations
uh on Build the Bear. So, like that was
basically my plan. And I I feel like
there's so many things you could do with
the bear. Like there's just a lot of
stuff you can do to make it even more
fun and more dynamic to have not just
kids going in, but have more adults
going in all the time doing stuff. So, I
mean, you know how many like adult women
do like all like the surprise stuff with
like Dude, it's it's
love it.
>> Yeah. And I I felt like Build-A-B Bear
Management didn't really fully
understand the culture of like like that
adult uh like treasure hunting or like
getting your niche thing like
collectible like limited release and
using those limited release schedules to
get more hype just to get people on the
brand in the store and then they happen
to get other stuff too.
>> Yeah, 100%. cuz the like the mom or
whatever goes in or someone goes in for
that little thing and they get a couple
presents for their niece or this or
that, right?
I'm not going to do it. But like but
like that would have been a fun one.
>> I would love to see a Camila take over.
>> Yeah. Not going to happen, guys. And I'm
just having fun doing what I do now. Now
I got to already I got to already deal
with all these the 30 or 40 million new
investors who are vibe investing,
critiquing everything I say every day.
What market are you most bullish on that
you can't invest in?
>> I think embodied AI is a tough one for
people to invest in. I could invest in
it, but most people can't because it's
still private, right?
>> Yeah. But if you could throw your money
into just like a generalized fund of a
certain market, what would it be?
>> I actually think it's it's content. You
know, I've talked about this guys. I
think we're going through a massive
transition from conventional content to
new media. I think the world of
podcasting and two guys and a mic, no
offense here, but I think was podcasting
1.0. I think the next kind of like phase
of entertainment, phase of media is
going to be something that kind of sits
between this first generation of
podcasting and what we know of as as TV.
And I think there are people who are
amazing content creators that are going
to be pushing the limits of that space
the next 5 years. And I think they will
become increasingly valuable as a lot of
the old school media companies are
looking to invest in like new media and
what that looks like. Because guys, we
it's actually crazy.
Nobody watches TV anymore. Like other
than maybe some sports and maybe some
like huge viral programming on Netflix,
>> nobody watches TV cuz I have not watched
one thing this year. I watch a few
episodes of of like Stacey's show with
my wife because it was like going back
to a time when some characters that we
knew from back in the day, but like I
can't do it. Like I'm on a text thread
with these guys who are like talking
about all these great TV shows, they're
all in their 40s and 50s. I'm like,
"Dude, that sounds really good." I start
I put the I can't do it. I put the show
on, I'm 10 minutes in, I'm back to
TikTok. I'm back to my short form media.
like my mind has been corrupted by short
form media and now but the learning from
that is every single 20some year old
that's their brain
>> but it's bad it's it's I've started to
really
uh notice it now and I've I've stopped
myself actually from watching shorts and
I've cut down dramatically because I
remember just looking around at everyone
is just like sitting there like a zombie
is like
you're
>> and it's in when you start to see it and
notice it. Someone was joking on Twitter
and they said that scrolling was like a
low class behavior. And when I saw when
when that it just clicked to me it's
like you will never see someone who's
like doing something who's really
successful sitting on their phone
scrolling
>> and it just like clicked for me. It's
like holy the amount of time that you
waste
>> scrolling. I hate myself for I mean it's
my job.
>> Yeah.
>> But I still hate myself for it. Cuz last
night I found myself scrolling for
Bethany Frankle Burning Man videos to
start up, which they did. And I was
like, dude, I hate myself so much. I
can't believe that like rather than
watching like one of these highquality
shows that my buddies are talking about,
I'm watching Bethany Frankle arriving at
Burning Man and I was like, "This is
disgusting. This is like the lowest of
all lowquality
behavior right now."
>> Bethany Frankle.
>> I don't know who she
>> dude. Wow. Guys,
>> I I had this talk with I had this talk
with someone a week ago about generation
gaps.
>> I have no idea. I've never seen her.
>> And and
>> yeah, dude, she's like she's from that
she's the OG from Housewives. She's like
huge on I mean I don't like her. Okay. I
hate watcher. I hate watcher as most
people do. But like sometimes I feel I
have a generation like divide with
people that are 15 20 years younger than
me cuz I'm still 10 years younger than
them in my brain. And like you guys
right now to me are my generation divide
but you're older than me instead of
you're actually 20 years younger than
me. Dude, how do you know who Bethany
Frankle is?
>> See, but this this is the problem.
>> This is the problem. Like when your mind
is melted on TikTok, that's all you
know. And it's disgusting. But I just
think we're going to look back like uh
cigarettes were so socially acceptable
back in the day and there's so many
things that we did that were like, "Oh
my god, we had no idea they were that
harmful." I think we'll look back at
shorts and the algorithm and scrolling
of the impact that has to your brain and
we're going to have a divide of people,
those who were raised on shorts and
those who were not.
>> And it's going to be like a birth defect
to some degree of like, oh, your parents
smoked. Well, you you know, well, they
were pregnant and you know, you don't
have as quite of a leg up as those whose
parents didn't do that.
>> I agree with you. It's really bad. I
feel terrible when I'm doing it. It's
just like,
>> can you stop? Could you stop yourself?
>> No.
>> Is it is it because you rationalize it
as research or is it an addiction or is
it like, hey, this gives me alpha in the
market and the market is the most
important and this gets me there.
>> Both are true. Like I have to do it cuz
I have to stay in the weeds of culture
and consumer behavior and what people
are talking about, what they're thinking
about, where they're going, what they're
spending their money on, what they care
about, how they spend their time, who
they want to give attention to. If I
lose that, then I lose my edge in the
market.
>> Mhm.
>> But sometimes I feel like I don't need
to do it as much as I do it. And I I
just can't stop because it's addictive.
It's a fullon
>> I think I think I think it is a it's
it's a chemical drug for your brain that
just it it uh it zombifi like it
liquefies
your brain and dumbs everything down.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's just it's a it's a numbing uh
cream basically for your mind.
>> I I think the only way for me to get out
is I'm going to have to dedicate time
away from it. Like someone was just
telling me so I'm in Austin every week
now for this whole podcast studio and
someone was telling me that Barton Creek
opens up like between 8 and 10 and you
could just go there and meditate and
journal. I'm not journaling, but like
I'm just going to when I'm in Austin,
I'm going to start going there to be
around other people that are not on
their phone and just doing stuff like
journaling and meditating to where I
will feel so guilty picking up my phone
if I'm just around those people that I
hope that's the way it is that I'm just
going to like be at one with my thoughts
and I don't know stretch or do
something.
>> What works really well for me is just
cutting out on like generalized screen
time as opposed to like intentional
screen time. So, for example, if you do
your deep research between like 10 p.m.
and 2 a.m., if you have that time
blocked out for, okay, I'm going to go
on TikTok. I'm going to do that like
check everything, read all these
comments, that's productive. Anything
outside of that, for example, in passing
instead of like noticing the beautiful
landscape as you're passing through some
place like walking to a coffee shop,
you're on your phone like scrolling on
TikTok. Like, I would say that's like
that part of that human experience that
we're all kind of here for. you're
missing that and you're trading that for
something that's actually pretty
valueless. Like we've said, that I think
is liquefying your brain more is like
removing that experience of like
noticing life than intentional time
between 10 p.m. and 2 a.m. that is spent
doing research to collect alpha in the
market. And the way that I intentionally
try to like or the way I try to segment
it and be more intentional at times and
less intentional at others is I just
make sure that like my color filter is
on on my phone to turn everything black
and white when I'm not intentionally
watching videos, doing social media, or
it's like intentional downtime. My
problem is I get somewhere early like to
the doctor's office and I have 10
minutes before my appointment and I'm
scrolling reals instead of like sitting
there and like existing with myself. I
mean that I think that makes a lot of
sense. And also I heard a guy say
recently that if you do the same thing
constantly every day, which is like
scrolling.
>> Yeah. That that that your life moves
quicker.
>> Yes. Your life compresses.
>> Compresses, which scared the hell out of
me. I was like,
>> I think it is true. I I thought about
it. I'm like, dude, that's been
happening to me. I need to change it up.
Like a lot of stuff. I think I'm going
to start going to like a different
coffee shop some mornings and just see
different people.
>> Minor things that make it I saw it was
like take a different way to work in the
morning. Uh take a walk instead of this.
>> See how boring this is?
>> What is that?
>> It's a hot dog.
>> Well, not that. I'm saying like if
you're like watching reals, do you see
how much more boring it is if it's in
black and white?
>> That's really good. You're right.
>> Like it's it it's
>> see it though. I'm so I'm such a
>> No, no, no, no, no. Like, you go on
reals and it makes you want to get off
of it. It really like you'll only last
five minutes doing this until until And
it pulls you out because a lot of the
times the problem is you open up your
phone, you swipe, you don't even look
where the Instagram app is. Your your
thumb just knows it. And so it's it's
like a second nature almost. If you
close out of a message tab with someone,
you go to your home feed just sitting on
your couch and your thumb automatically
navigates it its way to the Instagram
app and then to the reals and to the
messages like but if you do this it
makes you understand what you're doing
and forces consciousness and so this
will slow you down and then you can you
know turn off the color filter when you
have that time between 10 and 2. Try it
out for a couple days see if it works
>> or maybe don't turn it off that way like
you're intentionally staying on only as
long as you really need to be. True.
Yeah, it makes it just slightly less
enjoyable and more like research based.
>> I love it. I'll try it.
>> Guys, thank you so much for tuning in.
So, basically,
>> you know why we're here. We already
explained it in the beginning of the
episode. Thank you so much.
>> Thank you to Chris. This also Skyouse,
this is your studio.
>> You didn't really plan on hosting
podcasts here, but this is located in
Dallas. It's also going to be used as an
event space. So, if you want to rent out
a place to watch the Super Bowl, they
have this huge LED screen. If you guys
want to check it out, man, my whole
group, well, we'll book it for you.
>> If you want to hire Jack and I as an
appearance fee to show up at your Super
Bowl party, we'll be open to that, too.
>> I would do that.
>> You just have to pay for our stay at the
Embassy Suites.
>> That's it.
>> Thank you guys so much for watching.
>> Uh, the one with the king bed, by the
way, corner room.
>> Well, we both got when we came and it
was on our dime, what did we get? Two
full beds separated.
>> Full beds.
>> Non corner, by the way. That's fine.
>> The smoking room.
>> A little cheaper.
>> So, with that said, thank you so much.
Till next time. See you.